<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <BandNode.description>ამ მექანიტორის გამტარუნარიანობა იზრდება ზოლის კვანძის სტრუქტურის გავლენის წყალობით.</BandNode.description>
  <BandNode.label>ჯგუფის კვანძი (მორგებული)</BandNode.label>
  <ControlSublinkImplant.description>An implant which increases a mechanitor's control group count and the work speed of a mechanitor's mechs.\n\nThis implant can be installed up to 6 times to increase its effect.</ControlSublinkImplant.description>
  <ControlSublinkImplant.label>საკონტროლო ქვებმული</ControlSublinkImplant.label>
  <MechFormfeederImplant.description>An implant which increases the speed at which a mechanitor can produce mechs in a mech gestator. The processor optimizes the behavior of the mechanites in the mech forming tank.\n\nThis implant can be self-installed in the same way as the mechlink.\n\nThis implant can be installed up to 6 times to increase its effect.</MechFormfeederImplant.description>
  <MechFormfeederImplant.label>მექანიკური გესტაციის პროცესორი</MechFormfeederImplant.label>
  <MechlinkImplant.description>A bionic implant that allows direct control of mechanoids. Mechlinks are used by soldiers to control war mechs, and by workers to control labor mechs. A person with a mechlink is known as a mechanitor.\n\nMechlinks are self-installable. Pressed into the back of the throat, the unit injects itself through the flesh to clamp inside the base of the skull where it meets the spinal cord. There, it threads a web of ultrafine wires throughout nearby neuronal tissue to make the direct mental link between the user and the mechanoid control band.\n\nMechlinks are not simply devices for sending radio signals to mechanoids, because mechanoids are not merely robots. In addition to traditional computers, mechanoids have a dim psychic presence, so fluently controlling them requires a psychic connection. By linking mechanitor and mechanoid both psychically and electromagnetically, the mechlink permits deeper control than screen-and-button interfaces.\n\nSince the mechlink interlaces deep within the brain tissue, it can only be removed after death.\n\nNote: A mechanitor must be capable of smithing work to gestate mechanoids.</MechlinkImplant.description>
  <MechlinkImplant.label>მეჩლინკი</MechlinkImplant.label>
  <RemoteRepairerImplant.description>A mechlink upgrade which allows the mechanitor to repair mechs from a distance. The user links with the mechanoid and uses their own brain to psychically guide its self-repair mechanites.\n\nThis implant can be installed up to 3 times to increase its range.</RemoteRepairerImplant.description>
  <RemoteRepairerImplant.label>დისტანციური რემონტი</RemoteRepairerImplant.label>
  <RemoteShielderImplant.description>An implant which allows the mechanitor to place a personal defense shield on a mech. The mechanitor must continuously focus on the mech in order to maintain the shield. It can be used to save a mech at a critical moment.\n\nThis implant can be installed up to 3 times to increase its range and shield energy.</RemoteShielderImplant.description>
  <RemoteShielderImplant.label>დისტანციური ფარი</RemoteShielderImplant.label>
  <RepairProbeImplant.description>An implant which increases a mechanitor's mech repair speed. This does not affect the overall energy needed to repair a mechanoid.\n\nThe implant allows the mechanitor to plug directly into a mechanoid while repairing it and better-direct the mech's self-repair mechanites.\n\nThis implant can be installed up to 6 times to increase its effect.</RepairProbeImplant.description>
  <RepairProbeImplant.label>სარემონტო ზონდი</RepairProbeImplant.label>
</LanguageData>
