<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Chimera.description>A huge creature that resembles a disfigured combination of a bear and other animals. It is vicious without limit.\n\nIt's not known if this is a combination of natural animals or a poor imitation of animal life created by an insane machine mind.</Chimera.description>
  <Chimera.label>ქიმერა</Chimera.label>
  <Devourer.description>მასიური ურჩხული უფსკრული დაკბილული თაიგულით და სქელი, გველის მსგავსი სხეულით. მჭამელს შეუძლია სხეულის სიგრძეზე რამდენჯერმე ხტუნვა, რომ ადამიანი მთლიანად გადაყლაპოს. კუჭის ძლიერი მჟავები სწრაფად შთანთქავს ჯერ კიდევ ცოცხალ მსხვერპლს. ნაშთები მალევე რეგურგირდება.</Devourer.description>
  <Devourer.label>მჭამელი</Devourer.label>
  <FleshmassNucleus.description>The archotech core of a fleshmass heart. It is a chaotic lattice of fluid-smeared metal. Solid chunks of jagged metal appear here and there, packed with archotechnology. The whole structure slowly twists and bends under its own power.\n\nIt constantly grows meat on its surface, which occasionally erupts violently. If too much meat builds up, it will regrow into a fleshmass heart.</FleshmassNucleus.description>
  <FleshmassNucleus.label>ხორცის მასის ბირთვი</FleshmassNucleus.label>
  <Gorehulk.description>A monstrous creature that resembles a massive, painfully swollen human with randomly reconfigured body parts. Near its top is a stretched face that watches its victim with dead eyes.\n\nHundreds of sharp keratin spines protrude from the gorehulk's skin. It can launch these spines to spear its victims at a distance. However, its awkward fleshy body is less effective at causing harm up close.\n\nIt's hard to know whether this is a human that was horribly distorted by the influence of the void or a poor imitation of humanity created from scratch by some evil intelligence.</Gorehulk.description>
  <Gorehulk.label>გორჰულკი</Gorehulk.label>
  <Metalhorror.description>A horrific shifting mass of metal filaments, blades, and instruments. This metal is maintained and regenerated by a circulating dark fluid.\n\nWhile dormant, fluid metalhorrors are hidden in a host body. They use their host to infect others, creating more metalhorrors. If detected or endangered, the metalhorror will form a jagged exoskeleton and cut its way out of the host's flesh.\n\nAn emerged metalhorror will eventually enter a low-energy hibernating state if left undisturbed.</Metalhorror.description>
  <Metalhorror.label>მეტალჰორორი</Metalhorror.label>
  <Nociosphere.description>A dark metallic sphere covered with curved and jagged grooves. The sphere emanates sensations of pain. It hurts to be near it.\n\nThe sphere thrums with a mysterious energy. It appears to be increasing in activity. It's not clear what will happen when it reaches its full capacity. However, if you capture it, you can decrease its activity by suppressing it.</Nociosphere.description>
  <Nociosphere.label>ნოციოსფერო</Nociosphere.label>
  <Noctol.description>მსხვილი, მღელვარე არსება დაფარულია ცხიმიანი შავი კარაფით და შეიარაღებული კლანჭებით, რომლებიც წარმოიქმნება ბიოფერიტებისგან. სანამ ის სიბნელეში მომაკვდინებელია, სინათლის ზემოქმედება აღიზიანებს მის თვალებსა და ხორცს, რაც მნიშვნელოვნად ანელებს მას.</Noctol.description>
  <Noctol.label>ნოქტოლი</Noctol.label>
  <Revenant.description>A spindly figure of desiccated skin stretched over an impossibly tall humanoid frame. The revenant's name comes from its pattern of returning to hypnotize new people each night.\n\nOutlander folklore describes an invisible spectre that captures the minds of sinners, placing them in a living hell. In the story, the victims can only be returned to life by hunting the creature as it sleeps and killing it.\n\nA hidden revenant can be revealed with disruptor flares, explosives, EMP, firefoam, or fire.</Revenant.description>
  <Revenant.label>გამობრუნებული</Revenant.label>
  <Sightstealer.description>გაფითრებული და გაუფორმებელი ჰუმანოიდები. მათი მკლავები ბოლოვდება ბასრი, დახვეული კლანჭებით, რომლებიც წარმოიქმნება ბიოფერიტისგან. სანახაობრივი მტაცებლები მყიფეები არიან, მაგრამ იყენებენ ფსიქიკურ გავლენას, რათა თავი უხილავი გახდნენ, სანამ მსხვერპლს არ მიახლოვდებიან. ცნობილია, რომ ისინი აფრქვევენ შემზარავ ყვირილს, როდესაც ისინი იკრიბებიან თავიანთ საშინელ ნადირობისას.</Sightstealer.description>
  <Sightstealer.label>სანახაობის მძარცველი</Sightstealer.label>
</LanguageData>
