<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <Blindness_Cult.description>Blindless opens the inner eye, and suffering illuminates the true sight.\n\nUnlocks the medical specialist role. Will have sacrifices, ritual blindings and scarifications. These people have reduced comfort expectations.</Blindness_Cult.description>
  <Blindness_Cult.label>სიბრმავე კულტი</Blindness_Cult.label>
  <Cannibals.description>The flesh of man and woman is the highest form of sustenance. Also, it's just delicious.\n\nWill have gladiator duels, prisoner sacrifices, and human meat feasts.</Cannibals.description>
  <Cannibals.label>კანიბალები</Cannibals.label>
  <ClassicLike.description>თქვენი კოლონისტები იღებენ რწმენის სისტემას, როგორიცაა კლასიკური RimWorld. დანარჩენ მსოფლიოს აქვს მათთვის გამომუშავებული ცალკეული იდეოლიგიები.</ClassicLike.description>
  <ClassicLike.label>კლასიკური მსგავსი</ClassicLike.label>
  <Cowboys.description>Men should keep a strong grip over their herds and their women. Raising animals for food is much better than farming plants. We don't tolerate arguments about any of this.\n\nUnlocks the animals specialist role.</Cowboys.description>
  <Cowboys.label>კოვბოები</Cowboys.label>
  <Criminal_Gang.description>Following someone else's ideas and working all day are for weaklings. This group thrives on raiding others and contact with diverse ideas.\n\nUnlocks melee and shooting specialist roles. Will have gladiator duels.</Criminal_Gang.description>
  <Criminal_Gang.label>კრიმინალური ბანდა</Criminal_Gang.label>
  <Domination_Gang.description>Our beliefs are law and truth. We will try to convince them. Anyone who resists our teaching is a vile subhuman who must be crushed.\n\n Unlocks melee and shooting specialist roles. Will have gladiator duels.</Domination_Gang.description>
  <Domination_Gang.label>ბატონობის ბანდა</Domination_Gang.label>
  <Feminine_Ravagers.description>Women should assert their natural power by reigning over men and pillaging weaker peoples.\n\nUnlocks melee and shooting specialist roles. Will have gladiator duels.</Feminine_Ravagers.description>
  <Feminine_Ravagers.label>ქალური მძარცველები</Feminine_Ravagers.label>
  <Feral_People.description>We are animals and animals are us. We are trees and we live by them and love them as us.\n\nUnlocks animal and plants specialist roles. Increases taming abilities of every member. Cutting trees and slaughtering animals are unacceptable. These people can connect more deeply with the Gauranlen trees.</Feral_People.description>
  <Feral_People.label>ველური ხალხი</Feral_People.label>
  <Free_Ranchers.description>A community of ranchers who hunt and raise animals for food. They don't like eating plants. They welcome diverse ideas.\n\nUnlocks the animals specialist role.</Free_Ranchers.description>
  <Free_Ranchers.label>თავისუფალი რანჩერები</Free_Ranchers.label>
  <High_Collectivists.description>Everyone must work hard and contribute to the community, so they can party in a smokeleaf circle together.\n\nUnlocks the plants specialist role.</High_Collectivists.description>
  <High_Collectivists.label>მაღალი კოლექტივისტები</High_Collectivists.label>
  <Human_Purists.description>The human race is superior and the human body is sacred. We disdain body modification, scarification and drug use.\n\nUnlocks the medical and production specialist roles.</Human_Purists.description>
  <Human_Purists.label>ადამიანის პურისტები</Human_Purists.label>
  <Martyrs.description>ჩვენი კორუმპირებული, ცოდვილი ბუნების აღიარება მისთვის ისეთივე მნიშვნელოვანია, როგორც ტანჯვა. ტკივილი და მსხვერპლი მოწონებულია, ხოლო ფიზიკური სიყვარული და კომფორტი სამარცხვინოა.</Martyrs.description>
  <Martyrs.label>მოწამეები</Martyrs.label>
  <Mole_People.description>The sun - it stuns, we shun! In the tunnels we shuffle, and snuffle for truffles. In our bubble there's no scuttling trouble. Never a kerfuffle.\n\nGrants increased mining efficiency but an aversion to outdoor light.</Mole_People.description>
  <Mole_People.label>მოლი ხალხი</Mole_People.label>
  <Naked_Maneaters.description>Cannibal feasts are much better when both you and the meal are naked. It's almost like you can merge into one.\n\nIncludes sacrifices and gladiator duels.</Naked_Maneaters.description>
  <Naked_Maneaters.label>შიშველი მანეტერები</Naked_Maneaters.label>
  <NatureOverMan.description>We atone for humanity's crimes against nature by respecting her, and by performing acts of charity. Slaughtering animals and cutting trees are unacceptable.\n\nUnlocks plants specialist role.</NatureOverMan.description>
  <NatureOverMan.label>ბუნება ადამიანზე</NatureOverMan.label>
  <Nudist_Recruiters.description>ჩვენ უნდა ვიკამათოთ შემაკავებელი ტანსაცმლისგან და მუდმივად მოვიწვიოთ სხვები შემოგვიერთდნენ.</Nudist_Recruiters.description>
  <Nudist_Recruiters.label>ნუდისტი რეკრუტერები</Nudist_Recruiters.label>
  <Painful_Purists.description>Suffering purifies and ennobles. Modifying the body to ease your life is the way of the filthy.\n\nUnlocks the medical specialist role. These people have reduced comfort expectations. Will have gladiator duels and sacrifices.</Painful_Purists.description>
  <Painful_Purists.label>პურისტი ფლაგელატორები</Painful_Purists.label>
  <Progressive_Humanism.description>The human race is at the peak of nature and must use technology to step beyond. We do this by enhancing our bodies with technology, but we like to hear others' view on the matter.\n\nUnlocks research and production specialist roles.</Progressive_Humanism.description>
  <Progressive_Humanism.label>ტრანსცენდენტული ჰუმანისტები</Progressive_Humanism.label>
  <ProHuman_Darklovers.description>The human race flourishes in the darkness of night and the underground.\n\nUnlocks mining and production specialist roles. Combat efficiency in the dark is increased.</ProHuman_Darklovers.description>
  <ProHuman_Darklovers.label>ბნელი ადამიანები</ProHuman_Darklovers.label>
  <Techno_Utopians.description>The human body must be enhanced with technology so we can build a better future for everyone.\n\nUnlocks the research specialist role.</Techno_Utopians.description>
  <Techno_Utopians.label>ტექნოუტოპისტები</Techno_Utopians.label>
  <Tree_Worshippers.description>We live in harmony with the Gauranlen trees. Trees should never be cut, and animals should not be harmed.\n\n Unlocks the plants specialist role. These people live in rough conditions without complains, and can connect more deeply with the Gauranlen trees.</Tree_Worshippers.description>
  <Tree_Worshippers.label>ხეების თაყვანისმცემლები</Tree_Worshippers.label>
  <Unity_Family.description>საზოგადოება შრომისმოყვარე, თანამოაზრე ადამიანების ოჯახია. საკუთარი თავის პირველ ადგილზე დაყენება მიუღებელია.</Unity_Family.description>
  <Unity_Family.label>ერთიანი ოჯახი</Unity_Family.label>
  <Violent_Dominators.description>The weak deserve to lose what they have to us. Raiding and enslaving are honorable.\n\nUnlocks melee and shooting specialist roles. Will have gladiator duels.</Violent_Dominators.description>
  <Violent_Dominators.label>სისხლიანი დომინატორები</Violent_Dominators.label>
</LanguageData>
